{"data":[{"question":"As Ingrid Bergman lived a life of courage, she also approached die with courage.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"As","b":"a life","c":"she","d":"die","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Die-> death","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Residents in some sites can call an electrical inspector to have the wiring in their house is checked.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"sites","b":"an","c":"to have","d":"is checked","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Is checked-> checked","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"The best way to eliminate a pest is to controlling the food accessible to it.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The best","b":"to controlling","c":"food accessible","d":"it","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n\n- To controlling-> to control","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"The Earth depends the sun for its heating.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"depends","c":"sun for","d":"heating","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Depends-> depends on","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"The famous aviator Chales Lindbergh was a early supporter of rocket research.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"famous aviator","b":"a","c":"supporter","d":"rocket research","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- A-> an","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Cholesterol help the body by making hormones and building cell walls, but too much cholesterol can cause heart problems.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"help","b":"by making","c":"too much","d":"can cause","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Help-> helps","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Luther Burand was a pioneer in the process of graft immature plants onto fully mature plants.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"a pioneer","b":"graft","c":"fully","d":"plants","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Graft-> grafting","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"With its compound eyes, dragonflies can see moving insects approximately 18 feet away.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"its","b":"moving","c":"approximately","d":"feet","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Its-> their","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"An X-ray microscope enables a person to see on solid materials such as metal and bone.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"enables","b":"on","c":"such as","d":"bone","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- On-> through","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"The United States has a younger population as most other major industrial countries.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has","b":"as","c":"other","d":"countries","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- As-> than","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"}]}